export default data = [
  {
      question: "Martha has been trying to ______ her roommate since their quarrel last week, as she doesn’t want to continue the argument.",
      options: ["overgrow","bother","pursue","avoid"],
      correct_option: "avoid"
  },
  {
      question: "As David finished the last drop of the delicious chicken soup, he licked his lips and gave out sounds of ______.",
      options: ["contentment","dominance","explosion","affection"],
      correct_option: "contentment"
  },
  {
      question: "After several rounds of intense fighting, the boxer punched his ______ right in the face, knocked him out, and won the match.",
      options: ["performer","attendant","opponent","messenger"],
      correct_option: "opponent"
  },
  {
      question: "Watch out! The bench has just been painted. You can fan the wet paint if you want to ______ its drying.",
      options: ["fasten","hasten","lengthen","strengthen"],
      correct_option: "hasten"
  },
  {
      question: "Warm milk ______ sleepiness. So if you have trouble falling asleep, try drinking some warm milk before going to bed.",
      options: ["conceals","recruits","absorbs","induces"],
      correct_option: "induces"
  },
  {
      question: "Having worked five years as a data processor in a small town, Alice is tired of the routine of her job and the ______ of her life.",
      options: ["disturbance","salvation","remainder","monotony"],
      correct_option: "monotony"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter has never been on time to meetings or appointments. It would be interesting to look into reasons why he is ______ late.",
      options: ["chronically","hysterically","simultaneously","resistantly"],
      correct_option: "chronically"
  },
  {
      question: "The film Life of Pi won Ang Lee an Oscar in 2013 for Best Director—one of the most ______ awards in the movie industry.",
      options: ["populated","surpassed","coveted","rotated"],
      correct_option: "coveted"
  },
  {
      question: "According to environmental scientists, the earth is likely to experience significant ______ changes within the next century.",
      options: ["provincial","ecological","authentic","redundant"],
      correct_option: "ecological"
  },
  {
      question: "Traditional Chinese medical practices include ______ remedies, which use plants, plant parts, or a mixture of these to prevent or cure diseases.",
      options: ["herbal","frantic","magnetic","descriptive"],
      correct_option: "herbal"
  },
]